tradespoon.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Tradespoon

Tradespoon.com understands the importance of privacy and security to our subscribers. Tradespoon.com is committed to protecting the privacy of all our visitors and subscribers. Your right to privacy is very important to us. When you choose to provide us with information about yourself, we recognize that you trust us to act in a responsible manner.

**USAGE OF INFORMATION**

Any information you provide to us is maintained and accessible only by our Websites. Tradespoon.com uses this information to send you information and updates. We do not disclose any information about any individual user to entities outside of those partners except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. Tradespoon.com does not sell, rent, or lease any user information that it has collected over this website without permission. We do on occasion run joint promotions with our business partners.

**COOKIE POLICY**

We may use cookies, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by our Cookie Policy.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS**

The Site may send emails that contain links to third-party websites and and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot uarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and provdiing any information to any third-party websites, yo ushould inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those stepas necessary to, in your discreation, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content, or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, inclduing other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site.

**CANADIAN RESIDENTS**

To comply to the legislation of CASL, we only add users to our mailing list that checked a checkbox on our opt-in pages giving us express consent to receive further communications from Tradespoon.

**YOUR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:

If you wish to access, correct, update, or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing support@tradespoon.com.

In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by emailing support@tradespoon.com.

You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please contact us by emailing support@tradespoon.com.

Similarly, if we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

**OPT-OUT FROM MAIL LIST**

At any time you may request to be removed from our mailing list by clicking the unsubscribe link provided in each newsletter.

If you have any questions or concerns, we invite you to contact us [info@tradespoon.com](mailto:info@tradespoon.com)
